<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>North Houston .NET Users Group</title>
    <description>A programmers meetup</description>
    <link>https://www.nhdnug.org/</link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.nhdnug.org/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 01:45:15 +0000</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 01:45:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.10.0</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Software then and now: a personal journey</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I started my first software company in 1982 and have been an active developer for more than 40 years. What were the challenges back then compared to the present day? How has the business changed? What have I learned that still apply today?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;date-change&quot;&gt;Date Change&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;NORMALLY, we do the third Thursday of every month - but in order to accommodate our speaker’s schedule we’re doing April 24th instead.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;food--drinks&quot;&gt;Food / Drinks&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Food and drinks will be provided! Please contact us (on meetup) if you have any dietary restrictions/food allergies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;directions-and-parking-instructions&quot;&gt;Directions and Parking Instructions&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Meeting will be held in the offices of SmartDraw Software, 1780 Hughes Landing Blvd #1100 on the 11th floor.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.nhdnug.org/meetings/2025/04/24/software-then-and-now</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nhdnug.org/meetings/2025/04/24/software-then-and-now</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Lightning Talks!</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;We are doing something a little different for our March 2025 meetup: Lightning Talks⚡⚡⚡!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have a topic that is .NET or .NET-adjacent (i.e. front-end, testing, architecture, cloud, etc) that you’re passionate about but you’re not sure you can give a full 45-60 minute presentation then this is your chance - we’re going to select 3 Lightning talks that are 15-20 minutes apiece.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;our-lightning-talk-lineup&quot;&gt;Our Lightning Talk Lineup&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’re excited to announce our speakers for this event:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;roslyn-powered-standards-automate-team-conventions&quot;&gt;Roslyn-Powered Standards: Automate Team Conventions&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Speaker:&lt;/strong&gt; Peter Hellmuth, Solution Support Engineer at 3E&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Learn how to design custom Roslyn analyzers to enforce your team’s coding standards, transforming red squiggles into proactive code reviews that begin before you even commit. Develop quick fixes that allow developers to resolve violations with a single click, improving efficiency and consistency. For non-negotiable rules, integrate analyzers into your CI/CD pipeline to catch issues early and enforce standards before code merges.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Level: Introductory and overview&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Topics: C#, Continuous Delivery, Tooling, Patterns &amp;amp; Best Practices&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;semantic-search-with-sql-server&quot;&gt;Semantic Search with SQL Server&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Speaker:&lt;/strong&gt; Travis Plummer, Developer at SmartDraw&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Looking to show how we can enhance everyday search with Natural Language Processing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Level: Intermediate&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Topics: C#, Architecture&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;supercharge-your-net-testing-with-ncrunch&quot;&gt;Supercharge Your .NET Testing with NCrunch&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Speaker:&lt;/strong&gt; Tony Cardella, Software Engineer / Software Engineering Capability Lead at BJSS&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tired of waiting for tests to run? NCrunch is a powerful continuous testing tool for .NET that runs your tests in the background, providing instant feedback, real-time code coverage, and parallel execution to speed up development. In this lightning talk, we’ll explore how NCrunch works, highlight its key features, and see it in action with a quick demo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Level: Introductory and overview&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Topics: C#, Testing, Tooling&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If this sounds like fun, please submit our speaker interest form here: &lt;a href=&quot;https://forms.gle/aVzeVpvVhAkdfWLy7&quot;&gt;https://forms.gle/aVzeVpvVhAkdfWLy7&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;food--drinks&quot;&gt;Food / Drinks&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Food and drinks will be provided! Please contact us (on meetup) if you have any dietary restrictions/food allergies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;directions-and-parking-instructions&quot;&gt;Directions and Parking Instructions&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Meeting will be held in the offices of SmartDraw Software, 1780 Hughes Landing Blvd #1100 on the 11th floor.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.nhdnug.org/meetings/2025/03/20/lightning-talks</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nhdnug.org/meetings/2025/03/20/lightning-talks</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Null, The Absence of a Reference in C#</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Have you ever encountered a “possible deference of null reference” in your code and ignored it? How often does application telemetry show Null Reference Exceptions in your production environment? Do you even know what null is?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During this talk we will explore what &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;null&lt;/code&gt; is, how C# handles it, and some tools and practices to keep you from having failing code in production that can be handled during your development cycles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;food--drinks&quot;&gt;Food / Drinks&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Food and drinks will be provided! Please contact us (on meetup) if you have any dietary restrictions/food allergies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;directions-and-parking-instructions&quot;&gt;Directions and Parking Instructions&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Meeting will be held in the offices of SmartDraw Software, 1780 Hughes Landing Blvd #1100 on the 11th floor.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.nhdnug.org/meetings/2025/02/20/null-absence-of-a-reference</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nhdnug.org/meetings/2025/02/20/null-absence-of-a-reference</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Introduction to the Actor Model with Akka.NET</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The actor model is an old computer science concept, originating in 1973 - and it laid dormant is largely a thought experiment for most of its history until the rise of the Internet. Now in the era of cheap, commodity cloud computing the actor model is staging a major comeback across all programming languages and runtimes, both for building distributed systems and for creating reactive mobile or desktop applications.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this talk we will introduce the actor model through the use of &lt;a href=&quot;https://getakka.net/&quot;&gt;Akka.NET&lt;/a&gt;, the most popular distributed actor model framework in .NET. We’ll talk about what sorts of problems it solves well, when you should use it, and what are some of the adoption costs and overhead involved in using a tool like &lt;a href=&quot;https://getakka.net/&quot;&gt;Akka.NET&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;food--drinks&quot;&gt;Food / Drinks&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Food and drinks will be provided! Please contact us (on meetup) if you have any dietary restrictions/food allergies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;directions-and-parking-instructions&quot;&gt;Directions and Parking Instructions&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Meeting will be held in the offices of SmartDraw Software, 1780 Hughes Landing Blvd #1100 on the 11th floor.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.nhdnug.org/meetings/2025/01/16/actor-model-akka.net</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nhdnug.org/meetings/2025/01/16/actor-model-akka.net</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>.NET Conf 2024 &amp; NHDNUG Holiday Party</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Join NHDNUG for our 2024 Holiday Party and a live .NET Conf 2024 watch party at Spring Creek BBQ! We’re treating all registered attendees to a delicious BBQ dinner, so bring your appetite and your love for .NET!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’ll be recapping and replaying the best moments from .NET Conf, which airs live from November 12-14. Come enjoy great food, exciting .NET news, and festive networking with fellow members. It’s the perfect way to celebrate the season!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;food--drinks&quot;&gt;Food / Drinks&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;NHDNUG will cover the cost of your meal and a non-alcoholic beverage - just swing by the private banquet room to grab your meal ticket first.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Want a beer? Spring Creek has plenty, but it’s on your tab. Cheers!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;directions-and-parking-instructions&quot;&gt;Directions and Parking Instructions&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’ll be meeting in the Banquet Room at Spring Creek BBQ in Shenandoah - just look for the NHDNUG signs.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.nhdnug.org/meetings/2024/12/05/.net-conf-2024-and-holiday-party</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nhdnug.org/meetings/2024/12/05/.net-conf-2024-and-holiday-party</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Why Is All of My Data Stored in Parquet? (A Deep Dive into the Data Lake)</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Apache Parquet is a data format for efficient storage and retrieval of massive quantities of data that has been popularized by widespread adoption of the “data lake” architecture. The title of this talk is a question I asked of a coworker (a data engineer) in the process of consolidating our reporting and inference models onto a new analytics platform. The short answer, “because Databricks”, didn’t satisfy me. I was accustomed to traditional SQL, executing ad hoc queries from any language or platform I chose.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The long answer comes from a months-long investigation into how to read and write Parquet files from my favorite languages (C# and F#) and a growing appreciation of the format’s flexibility. I hope to convey more than just the Parquet specification, but also the ““how”” of parsing and writing Parquet and ““why”” this data format is so popular. I want to spark a discussion on the value of open-source data formats and how to avoid vendor lock-in for data access.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;food--drinks&quot;&gt;Food / Drinks&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Food and drinks will be provided! Please contact us (on meetup) if you have any dietary restrictions/food allergies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;directions-and-parking-instructions&quot;&gt;Directions and Parking Instructions&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Meeting will be held in the offices of SmartDraw Software, 1780 Hughes Landing Blvd #1100 on the 11th floor.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.nhdnug.org/meetings/2024/11/21/why-is-all-of-my-data-stored-in-parquet</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nhdnug.org/meetings/2024/11/21/why-is-all-of-my-data-stored-in-parquet</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>TDD for People</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Has this ever happened to you? You’re in a meeting, and you and your colleagues just can’t seem to get each other. You’ve shared all the relevant data, and the solution seems obvious to you… But there they go again heading off in some completely esoteric and unintelligible way. Frustrating right? It’s a little like what happens when you write some code, only to find it misbehaving in production right?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As developers we solved misbehaving code with Unit Tests. WE adjusted the way we develop so we could get more predictable outcomes. WE invented TDD. What if there was a way to apply to that those confusing and often frustrating conversations with our colleagues? What if we could test our conversations as we make them to get to better results? Let’s talk about how we might apply the Ladder of Inference to help us test and verify our conversations and our conclusions as we make them!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;food--drinks&quot;&gt;Food / Drinks&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Food and drinks will be provided! Please contact us (on meetup) if you have any dietary restrictions/food allergies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;directions-and-parking-instructions&quot;&gt;Directions and Parking Instructions&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Meeting will be held in the offices of SmartDraw Software, 1780 Hughes Landing Blvd #1100 on the 11th floor.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.nhdnug.org/meetings/2024/10/17/tdd-for-people</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nhdnug.org/meetings/2024/10/17/tdd-for-people</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>gRPC + .NET: Lessons from the Trenches</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Come find out what gRPC is, when you should use it, when you shouldn’t use it, and how to work around some of it’s limitations. Plus, we’ll go over how we used it (with .NET) to deliver a microservices architecture at one of the largest Oil &amp;amp; Gas companies in the greater Houston, Texas area to support their trading operations. Plus, you will learn a few ideas that will help make your implementation of gRPC easier!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;food--drinks&quot;&gt;Food / Drinks&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Food and drinks will be provided! Please contact us (on meetup) if you have any dietary restrictions/food allergies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;directions-and-parking-instructions&quot;&gt;Directions and Parking Instructions&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Meeting will be held in the offices of SmartDraw Software, 1780 Hughes Landing Blvd #1100 on the 11th floor.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.nhdnug.org/meetings/2024/09/19/grpc-.net-lesson-from-the-trenches</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nhdnug.org/meetings/2024/09/19/grpc-.net-lesson-from-the-trenches</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Rare, Medium, or Well Done? Finding the right level of DONE in Software Development</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;How would you feel if you ordered a steak expecting it to be cooked to medium but ended up receiving it well done? It sounds like a big missed-steak to me! I mean, steak puns are rarely well done.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In all seriousness, finding the right level of done in software development isn’t as easy as “Rare, medium, or well done?” and we are going to talk about why that is while providing some tools to get it just right.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;food--drinks&quot;&gt;Food / Drinks&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Food and drinks will be provided! Please contact us (on meetup) if you have any dietary restrictions/food allergies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;directions-and-parking-instructions&quot;&gt;Directions and Parking Instructions&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Meeting will be held in the offices of SmartDraw Software, 1780 Hughes Landing Blvd #1100 on the 11th floor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Enter through the main doors of the building and take the elevator to the 11th floor; the door to SmartDraw’s suite is in the elevator lobby on the 11th floor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you arrive at 1780 Hughes Landing after 6pm a member of the SmartDraw team will help you enter the building then travel up to the 11th floor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;parking&quot;&gt;Parking:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Park in the garage directly opposite. You’ll need to take a ticket to enter but there is no fee to leave - parking is free.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.nhdnug.org/meetings/2024/08/15/rare-medium-or-well-done</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nhdnug.org/meetings/2024/08/15/rare-medium-or-well-done</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>High Optionality Programming: Architectural Choices That Mitigate Technical Debt</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;“High Optionality Programming” - the practice of paying a small design &amp;amp; programming premium today in order to avoid a massive accumulation of technical debt later. This is a technique we’ve successfully used at large scale in our previous business and in the businesses of many of our customers. The key to implementing high optionality programming correctly is to assess the likelihood of a future change to your system and to plan for its eventuality in advance when it’s cheap to do so: early on in the software development lifecycle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this talk we explain the concepts behind high optionality programming, offer some case studies of how it’s been used successfully, and introduce the techniques that actively curb the long-term accumulation of technical debt in software projects.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;food--drinks&quot;&gt;Food / Drinks&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Food and drinks will be provided! Please contact us (on meetup) if you have any dietary restrictions/food allergies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;directions-and-parking-instructions&quot;&gt;Directions and Parking Instructions&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Meeting will be held in the offices of SmartDraw Software, 1780 Hughes Landing Blvd #1100 on the 11th floor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Enter through the main doors of the building and take the elevator to the 11th floor; the door to SmartDraw’s suite is in the elevator lobby on the 11th floor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you arrive at 1780 Hughes Landing after 6pm a member of the SmartDraw team will help you enter the building then travel up to the 11th floor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;parking&quot;&gt;Parking:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Park in the garage directly opposite. You’ll need to take a ticket to enter but there is no fee to leave - parking is free.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.nhdnug.org/meetings/2024/07/18/high-optionality-programming</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nhdnug.org/meetings/2024/07/18/high-optionality-programming</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
