<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>North Houston .NET Users Group</title>
    <description>A programmers meetup</description>
    <link>https://www.nhdnug.org/</link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.nhdnug.org/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2024 01:39:28 +0000</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2024 01:39:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.10.0</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>.NET Conf 2024 &amp; NHDNUG Holiday Party</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Join NHDNUG for our 2024 Holiday Party and a live .NET Conf 2024 watch party at Spring Creek BBQ! We’re treating all registered attendees to a delicious BBQ dinner, so bring your appetite and your love for .NET!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’ll be recapping and replaying the best moments from .NET Conf, which airs live from November 12-14. Come enjoy great food, exciting .NET news, and festive networking with fellow members. It’s the perfect way to celebrate the season!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;food--drinks&quot;&gt;Food / Drinks&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;NHDNUG will cover the cost of your meal and a non-alcoholic beverage - just swing by the private banquet room to grab your meal ticket first.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Want a beer? Spring Creek has plenty, but it’s on your tab. Cheers!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;directions-and-parking-instructions&quot;&gt;Directions and Parking Instructions&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’ll be meeting in the Banquet Room at Spring Creek BBQ in Shenandoah - just look for the NHDNUG signs.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.nhdnug.org/meetings/2024/12/05/.net-conf-2024-and-holiday-party</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nhdnug.org/meetings/2024/12/05/.net-conf-2024-and-holiday-party</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Why Is All of My Data Stored in Parquet? (A Deep Dive into the Data Lake)</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Apache Parquet is a data format for efficient storage and retrieval of massive quantities of data that has been popularized by widespread adoption of the “data lake” architecture. The title of this talk is a question I asked of a coworker (a data engineer) in the process of consolidating our reporting and inference models onto a new analytics platform. The short answer, “because Databricks”, didn’t satisfy me. I was accustomed to traditional SQL, executing ad hoc queries from any language or platform I chose.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The long answer comes from a months-long investigation into how to read and write Parquet files from my favorite languages (C# and F#) and a growing appreciation of the format’s flexibility. I hope to convey more than just the Parquet specification, but also the ““how”” of parsing and writing Parquet and ““why”” this data format is so popular. I want to spark a discussion on the value of open-source data formats and how to avoid vendor lock-in for data access.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;food--drinks&quot;&gt;Food / Drinks&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Food and drinks will be provided! Please contact us (on meetup) if you have any dietary restrictions/food allergies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;directions-and-parking-instructions&quot;&gt;Directions and Parking Instructions&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Meeting will be held in the offices of SmartDraw Software, 1780 Hughes Landing Blvd #1100 on the 11th floor.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.nhdnug.org/meetings/2024/11/21/why-is-all-of-my-data-stored-in-parquet</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nhdnug.org/meetings/2024/11/21/why-is-all-of-my-data-stored-in-parquet</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>TDD for People</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Has this ever happened to you? You’re in a meeting, and you and your colleagues just can’t seem to get each other. You’ve shared all the relevant data, and the solution seems obvious to you… But there they go again heading off in some completely esoteric and unintelligible way. Frustrating right? It’s a little like what happens when you write some code, only to find it misbehaving in production right?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As developers we solved misbehaving code with Unit Tests. WE adjusted the way we develop so we could get more predictable outcomes. WE invented TDD. What if there was a way to apply to that those confusing and often frustrating conversations with our colleagues? What if we could test our conversations as we make them to get to better results? Let’s talk about how we might apply the Ladder of Inference to help us test and verify our conversations and our conclusions as we make them!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;food--drinks&quot;&gt;Food / Drinks&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Food and drinks will be provided! Please contact us (on meetup) if you have any dietary restrictions/food allergies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;directions-and-parking-instructions&quot;&gt;Directions and Parking Instructions&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Meeting will be held in the offices of SmartDraw Software, 1780 Hughes Landing Blvd #1100 on the 11th floor.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.nhdnug.org/meetings/2024/10/17/tdd-for-people</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nhdnug.org/meetings/2024/10/17/tdd-for-people</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>gRPC + .NET: Lessons from the Trenches</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Come find out what gRPC is, when you should use it, when you shouldn’t use it, and how to work around some of it’s limitations. Plus, we’ll go over how we used it (with .NET) to deliver a microservices architecture at one of the largest Oil &amp;amp; Gas companies in the greater Houston, Texas area to support their trading operations. Plus, you will learn a few ideas that will help make your implementation of gRPC easier!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;food--drinks&quot;&gt;Food / Drinks&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Food and drinks will be provided! Please contact us (on meetup) if you have any dietary restrictions/food allergies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;directions-and-parking-instructions&quot;&gt;Directions and Parking Instructions&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Meeting will be held in the offices of SmartDraw Software, 1780 Hughes Landing Blvd #1100 on the 11th floor.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.nhdnug.org/meetings/2024/09/19/grpc-.net-lesson-from-the-trenches</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nhdnug.org/meetings/2024/09/19/grpc-.net-lesson-from-the-trenches</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Rare, Medium, or Well Done? Finding the right level of DONE in Software Development</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;How would you feel if you ordered a steak expecting it to be cooked to medium but ended up receiving it well done? It sounds like a big missed-steak to me! I mean, steak puns are rarely well done.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In all seriousness, finding the right level of done in software development isn’t as easy as “Rare, medium, or well done?” and we are going to talk about why that is while providing some tools to get it just right.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;food--drinks&quot;&gt;Food / Drinks&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Food and drinks will be provided! Please contact us (on meetup) if you have any dietary restrictions/food allergies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;directions-and-parking-instructions&quot;&gt;Directions and Parking Instructions&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Meeting will be held in the offices of SmartDraw Software, 1780 Hughes Landing Blvd #1100 on the 11th floor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Enter through the main doors of the building and take the elevator to the 11th floor; the door to SmartDraw’s suite is in the elevator lobby on the 11th floor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you arrive at 1780 Hughes Landing after 6pm a member of the SmartDraw team will help you enter the building then travel up to the 11th floor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;parking&quot;&gt;Parking:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Park in the garage directly opposite. You’ll need to take a ticket to enter but there is no fee to leave - parking is free.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.nhdnug.org/meetings/2024/08/15/rare-medium-or-well-done</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nhdnug.org/meetings/2024/08/15/rare-medium-or-well-done</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>High Optionality Programming: Architectural Choices That Mitigate Technical Debt</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;“High Optionality Programming” - the practice of paying a small design &amp;amp; programming premium today in order to avoid a massive accumulation of technical debt later. This is a technique we’ve successfully used at large scale in our previous business and in the businesses of many of our customers. The key to implementing high optionality programming correctly is to assess the likelihood of a future change to your system and to plan for its eventuality in advance when it’s cheap to do so: early on in the software development lifecycle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this talk we explain the concepts behind high optionality programming, offer some case studies of how it’s been used successfully, and introduce the techniques that actively curb the long-term accumulation of technical debt in software projects.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;food--drinks&quot;&gt;Food / Drinks&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Food and drinks will be provided! Please contact us (on meetup) if you have any dietary restrictions/food allergies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;directions-and-parking-instructions&quot;&gt;Directions and Parking Instructions&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Meeting will be held in the offices of SmartDraw Software, 1780 Hughes Landing Blvd #1100 on the 11th floor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Enter through the main doors of the building and take the elevator to the 11th floor; the door to SmartDraw’s suite is in the elevator lobby on the 11th floor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you arrive at 1780 Hughes Landing after 6pm a member of the SmartDraw team will help you enter the building then travel up to the 11th floor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;parking&quot;&gt;Parking:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Park in the garage directly opposite. You’ll need to take a ticket to enter but there is no fee to leave - parking is free.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.nhdnug.org/meetings/2024/07/18/high-optionality-programming</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nhdnug.org/meetings/2024/07/18/high-optionality-programming</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Property Based Testing in FsCheck</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Many of us who use automated tests will use Example Based Tests; these are tests in which we provide data – the examples that should pass. However there’s another less known, but very powerful testing style called Property Based Testing. In this style of testing, we provide properties – universal invariants that should hold regardless of input. As a result, we no longer specify examples, but let a framework choose examples for us. This gives us a different way to think about our tests and software.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This talk introduces Property Based Testing using FsCheck. FsCheck is a property based testing framework for .NET. While this talk uses F# for most examples, it will provide some examples in C# as well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;food--drinks&quot;&gt;Food / Drinks&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Food and drinks will be provided! Please contact us (on meetup) if you have any dietary restrictions/food allergies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;directions-and-parking-instructions&quot;&gt;Directions and Parking Instructions&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Meeting will be held in the offices of SmartDraw Software, 1780 Hughes Landing Blvd #1100 on the 11th floor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Enter through the main doors of the building and take the elevator to the 11th floor; the door to SmartDraw’s suite is in the elevator lobby on the 11th floor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you arrive at 1780 Hughes Landing after 6pm a member of the SmartDraw team will help you enter the building then travel up to the 11th floor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;parking&quot;&gt;Parking:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Park in the garage directly opposite. You’ll need to take a ticket to enter but there is no fee to leave - parking is free.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.nhdnug.org/meetings/2024/06/20/property-based-testing-in-fcheck</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nhdnug.org/meetings/2024/06/20/property-based-testing-in-fcheck</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>.NET Trivia Night</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Show off your .NET knowledge and battle for the .NET LeetCode trophy at our NHDNUG .NET Trivia Night!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Join us for an evening of fun, friendly rivalry, and retro arcade games on Thursday, May 16th at A Game Changer, located in downtown Conroe - just a 15 minute drive North of The Woodlands.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This event will not only be a battle of wits over .NET-related trivia questions, but an opportunity to engage in some friendly competition while enjoying a night out with fellow .NET enthusiasts. Attendees can organize into small teams or compete on their own, fostering a collaborative and competitive atmosphere as they vie for the ultimate trophy to proudly display in their office.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Come for the trivia, stay for the games, and leave with new connections - and possibly the ultimate symbol of .NET prowess!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;food--drinks&quot;&gt;Food / Drinks&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;NHDNUG will provide food, soft drinks, and wristbands for unlimited access to classic arcade games.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please check in at the front / bar area to receive your wristband - and be sure to let them know you’re attending Trivia Night.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Alcoholic beverages are available to purchase.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;directions-and-parking&quot;&gt;Directions and Parking&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This Meetup will be at A Game Changer, located at 109 MetCalf St, Conroe, TX 77301, in downtown Conroe - just 15 minutes North of The Woodlands.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ample parking is available in this charming downtown area.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.nhdnug.org/meetings/2024/05/16/.net-trivia.night</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nhdnug.org/meetings/2024/05/16/.net-trivia.night</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hands-on Machine Learning with Microsoft ML.NET</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;“ML.NET is a cross-platform machine learning framework by Microsoft that allows developers in the .NET ecosystem to perform advanced Machine Learning techniques. In this live software coding session, Michael will train and demonstrate several machine learning algorithms and techniques and provide commentary on effectiveness, metrics evaluation, and more.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Additionally, we will explore some online Azure AI services such as Image Detection and Generative AI with an LLM via Azure OpenAI. Everything from Machine Learning basics to a few advanced techniques will be covered, so come prepared to learn about the machine learning toolkit from Microsoft.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;food--drinks&quot;&gt;Food / Drinks&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Food and drinks will be provided! Please contact us (on meetup) if you have any dietary restrictions/food allergies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;directions-and-parking-instructions&quot;&gt;Directions and Parking Instructions&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Meeting will be held in the offices of SmartDraw Software, 1780 Hughes Landing Blvd #1100 on the 11th floor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Enter through the main doors of the building and take the elevator to the 11th floor; the door to SmartDraw’s suite is in the elevator lobby on the 11th floor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you arrive at 1780 Hughes Landing after 6pm a member of the SmartDraw team will help you enter the building then travel up to the 11th floor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;parking&quot;&gt;Parking:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Park in the garage directly opposite. You’ll need to take a ticket to enter but there is no fee to leave - parking is free.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.nhdnug.org/meetings/2024/04/18/hands-on-machine-learning-with-microsoft-ml.net</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nhdnug.org/meetings/2024/04/18/hands-on-machine-learning-with-microsoft-ml.net</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Resilient Unit Testing - Going beyond Arrange, Act, Assert</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;“Unit testing and TDD are designed to save time for the developers and testers while also reducing the risk of accidental bugs while implementing change. Yet, most teams either don’t use unit tests or found that they take more time than they save. But this doesn’t have to be your experience, and this session is going to cover the role of a unit test, how to build them to last, and other hidden benefits you can find along the way.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Come join as we crack open the code and discover a world beyond arrange, act, and assert.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;food--drinks&quot;&gt;Food / Drinks&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Food and drinks will be provided! Please contact us (on meetup) if you have any dietary restrictions/food allergies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;directions-and-parking-instructions&quot;&gt;Directions and Parking Instructions&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Meeting will be held in the offices of SmartDraw Software, 1780 Hughes Landing Blvd #1100 on the 11th floor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Enter through the main doors of the building and take the elevator to the 11th floor; the door to SmartDraw’s suite is in the elevator lobby on the 11th floor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you arrive at 1780 Hughes Landing after 6pm, a member of the SmartDraw team will help you enter then building then travel up to the 11th floor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;parking&quot;&gt;Parking:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Park in the garage directly opposite. You’ll need to take a ticket to enter but there is no fee to leave - parking is free.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.nhdnug.org/meetings/2024/03/21/resilient-unit-testing</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nhdnug.org/meetings/2024/03/21/resilient-unit-testing</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
